<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Destini</string>

    <string name="T1_Story">Your car has blown a tire on a winding road in the middle of nowhere with no cell phone reception. You decide to hitchhike. A rusty pickup truck rumbles to a stop next to you. A man with a wide brimmed hat with soulless eyes opens the passenger door for you and asks: \"Need a ride, boy?\". </string>
    <string name="T1_Ans1">I\'ll hop in. Thanks for the help! </string>
    <string name="T1_Ans2">Better ask him if he\'s a murderer first. </string>


    <string name="T2_Story">He nods slowly, unphased by the question.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans1">At least he\'s honest. I\'ll climb in.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans2">Wait, I know how to change a tire.</string>


    <string name="T3_Story">As you begin to drive, the stranger starts talking about his relationship with his mother. He gets angrier and angrier by the minute. He asks you to open the glovebox. Inside you find a bloody knife, two severed fingers, and a cassette tape of Elton John. He reaches for the glove box.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans1">I love Elton John! Hand him the cassette tape.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans2">It\'s him or me! You take the knife and stab him.</string>


    <string name="T4_End">What? Such a cop out! Did you know traffic accidents are the second leading cause of accidental death for most adult age groups?</string>
    <string name="T5_End">As you smash through the guardrail and careen towards the jagged rocks below you reflect on the dubious wisdom of stabbing someone while they are driving a car you are in.</string>
    <string name="T6_End">You bond with the murderer while crooning verses of "Can you feel the love tonight". He drops you off at the next town. Before you go he asks you if you know any good places to dump bodies. You reply: \"Try the pier.\"</string>


    <string name="T1_Story_ES">Tu coche ha quemado una llanta en un camino sinuoso en el medio de la nada sin cobertura en el móvil. Decides hacer autostop. Una camioneta oxidada retumba a tu lado. Un hombre con un sombrero de ala ancha con ojos sin alma le abre la puerta del pasajero y le pregunta: \"¿Necesita que lo lleve, muchacho?\".</string>
    <string name="T1_Ans1_ES">Sí, por favor. Gracias por la ayuda! </string>
    <string name="T1_Ans2_ES">Mejor pregúntale primero si es un asesino. </string>


    <string name="T2_Story_ES">Él asiente lentamente, sin contestar por la pregunta.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans1_ES">Al menos él es honesto. Voy a subir.</string>
    <string name="T2_Ans2_ES">Espera, sé cómo cambiar un neumático.</string>


    <string name="T3_Story_ES">Cuando empiezáis a conducir, el extraño comienza a hablar sobre su relación con su madre. Él se pone más y más furioso por el momento. Te pide que abras la guantera. Dentro encuentras un cuchillo ensangrentado, dos dedos cortados y una cinta de cassette de Elton John. Alcanza la guantera.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans1_ES">¡Me encanta Elton John! Dale la cinta de cassette.</string>
    <string name="T3_Ans2_ES">¡Es él o yo! Coges el cuchillo y lo apuñalas.</string>


    <string name="T4_End_ES">¿Qué? ¡No quiero ser cómplice! ¿Sabías que los accidentes de tráfico son la segunda causa principal de muerte accidental en la mayoría de los grupos de adultos?</string>
    <string name="T5_End_ES">A medida que rompe el quitamiedos y avanza hacia las rocas escarpadas que hay debajo, reflexionas sobre el hecho de apuñalar a alguien mientras conduce un coche en el que se encuentra.</string>
    <string name="T6_End_ES">Te alías con el asesino mientras cantas versos de \"¿Puedes sentir el amor esta noche?\". Te deja en la siguiente ciudad. Antes de irte te pregunta si conoces algún buen lugar para dejar los cuerpos. Respondes: \"Prueba el muelle\".</string>

</resources>